<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="102782" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Pandemic (TEST VERSION)" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Pandemic (TEST VERSION)" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<!--LongDescription Value="This is a long description" /-->
	<LongDescription>
TEST VERSION: Adds enhanced disease gameplay, including:
* Contagious sickness -- the contagious radius of a sick citizen is shown as a green circle; this can be turned off in settings
* Disease progression -- contagiousness and health impact increases by disease stage
* Tracking of disease strains; all sick citizens are assigned a disease strain upon becoming sick. Disease stats can be viewed in the health tab or disease control panel
* Random and configurable disease mutations -- disease have a chance to mutate into a new strain upon spread
* New 'Mask Mandate' city policy -- citizen adherence to mask mandates is based on eduction level
* Custom disease creator
* Immunity to strains recently contracted

All disease strains are mutations Base Disease Types:
* 1 - Common Cold
* 2 - Flu
* 3 - Novel

* An unlimited number of strains can exist per disease type; future versions will make it possible to create new base disease types.
* For vanilla disease lethality, set 2 and 3 to have zero spawn chance in the settings menu. The settings menu parameters only affect the disease configurations at game start; You can alter the parameters of the base diseases in-game in the control panel.
* A full-scale pandemic can easily be triggered by experimenting with the disease parameters

**TEST VERSION -- this mod is a work in progress**
The test version *does not affect savegames*; reloading a game will clear all disease configurations and reassign new diseases; savegame functionality will be added once the disease format is finalized.
The test version has not yet been optimized for large cities. 

The final version of the mod will also include:
* Vaccine research
* Quarantine / disaster shelter usage
* More random distribution types to use for mutation parameters (in this test version, all random variables are linear)
* UI improvements
* Performance optimizations
* Disease export
* Tourism affects on disease



	</LongDescription>
	<!--Thumbnail-->
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<!--Screenshot, can be set multiple times-->
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/pandemic1.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/pandemic2.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/pandemic3.jpg" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/pandemic4.jpg" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="https://forum.paradoxplaza.com/forum/threads/pandemic-test-version.1729680/" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="1.1" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.*.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog Value="Add settings option to disable disease info view of selected citizens." />
	<!--ChangeLog>
	</ChangeLog-->
	<!--External link. supported types are discord, github, youtube, twitch, x, paypal, patreon, buymeacoffee, kofi, crowdin, gitlab-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Vexal/CitiesSkylines2/tree/master/Pandemic" />
</Publish>
